<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[WorldWar2.5]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[WorldWar2.5]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/worldwar2-5/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 20:38:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/worldwar2-5/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Did Islam preserve Western Culture?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Did Islam preserve Western Culture?</h1><p>This is the common view, but, in fact, the facts seem to show something diametrically opposed: the spread of Islam came very close to destroying Western Civilization. Paradoxically, what saved it were the (much vilified) Crusades, which created the model of "Christian Europe", which, while still deeply divided, was Christian enough to resist the onslaught. See this video. Or this one.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/worldwar2-5/did-islam-preserve-western-culture/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5b81b51a-72f7-4890-bc6c-ab1c44694b26</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 20:37:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>It has been said that a distinguishing feature of the "Next" world war is that most people don't know it is in progess. The Next world war is one between Islam - a psychopathic ideology, which has managed to conquer much of the world over the last 1400 years, and Western civilization, which has been dominant in the world since, roughly, the middle of the eighteenth century, and previously for roughly five hundred years between the time of Alexander the Great and the decline of the Roman Empire - Western civilization was almost destroyed by Islam during the period of some six hundred years starting with the seventh century.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/worldwar2-5/cbadd633-ffce-4ba6-9491-f561fb54dc6e/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cbadd633-ffce-4ba6-9491-f561fb54dc6e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 18:58:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Here's the TRUE Non-Politically Correct History of Islam's Violence]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Here's the TRUE Non-Politically Correct History of Islam's Violence</h1><p>We have ISIS loyalists gunning down innocent French and American citizens. We have a President sending his Attorney General out to warn Americans to stifle their Free Speech rights. We have a shadowy American Muslim advocacy group blaming American citizens for bringing radical Islamic terrorism on ourselves.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4cc08151868f1c7096d878b1776c43444d043c47.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.thefederalistpapers.org/world/heres-the-true-non-politically-correct-history-of-islams-violence</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">457329f2-dbc2-435b-a349-01e6cc3fa24e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 18:42:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>